<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Deep Ford FATE</title>
    <link>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Deep Ford FATE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/character-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/character-creation/</guid>
      <description>Quick Character Creation Required   Come up with two permanent aspects: a high concept and a trouble.
Your high concept should be a classic character archetype. Since we’re at a supernatural college, those might be “vampire with a chip on her shoulder,” or “over-achieving warlock”.
Your trouble should be something that complicates your life. “Pursued by circus folk,” “Only keeping it together with ritual magic”, and “Can’t say no to a pretty face” are examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/setting/</guid>
      <description>Setting Vampires are real, of course. And ghosts and psychics and aliens. Those oddity shops supposedly built on ley lines where water runs uphill and two-headed cows are in jars? Ok, those aren’t real. But the ley lines are. And the owners probably do know someone with two heads.
But the earth is for the normals. Can’t have panic in the streets. And like most countries, America crawls from sea to shining sea with hunters, Pinkertons, and g-persons who harass and persecute the monsters to stay under the bed and keep the magical violence to a minimum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/trouble/</guid>
      <description>Some Trouble You Might Get Up To  Nobody’s heard from Cayce Library since before last summer. Officially it’s closed for renovation, but they don’t usually post twenty-four-hour campus security to guard construction sites. Well, not since they finished the Sexual Magic Department’s new parking lot a few years ago. Some enterprising students who wanted to get the scoop, or just spend a spooky night camped out in a weird old building, might take it upon themselves to break in and investigate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FATE for D&amp;D Players</title>
      <link>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/fate-for-dnd-players/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/fate-for-dnd-players/</guid>
      <description>FATE Cheatsheet for D&amp;amp;D Players The complete FATE Core rulebook is available here for pay-what-you-want.
Example character sheet here.
Aspects An aspect is a short, publicly-established English phrase that describes a reality about a character, location, or situation. Aspects can be gained and lost. Some are permanent and some are temporary. “Can’t turn down a bet,” “Runs like a dream if you can get it into gear,” “Full of bats,” and “Weighed down by books” are examples of aspects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCs and NPCs</title>
      <link>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/pcs-and-npcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hamptonsmith.github.io/deep-ford/docs/pcs-and-npcs/</guid>
      <description>PCs Chelsea (Sam Twyman) Untamed Pooka
No concept of what&amp;rsquo;s appropriate
Devin (Anthony Roesch) Psionic human/chthonian hybrid (product of a clandestine government experiment)
Are these hallucinations becoming manifest or am I just freaking crazy?
Ray von Piers (Sebastian Ebert) Bodybuilder-wannabe Vampire
Can&amp;rsquo;t for the life of him correctly cast &amp;ldquo;Protection from Sunlight&amp;rdquo;
NPCs Abatha Grace ???
???
Affiliations: Deep Ford College (President)
Ajay Mann Bodybuilding werewolf
Aggressively competitive
Affiliations: Deep Ford College (Student)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>